ourbabynamer.com 2018-05-28

# Privacy Policy

At OurBabyNamer.com we understand your need to maintain your privacy as you surf and shop on the internet. For this reason we are providing our privacy policy. This policy applies to the use by consumers of OurBabyNamer.com and governs online data collection and usage by OurBabyNamer.com only. 

What Information We CollectIn an effort to understand our visitors, analyze site traffic and continue to improve our business, the following information may be collected: IP address, browser type, domain name, access times and referring web site. 

Links To Partner And Advertiser SitesOurBabyNamer.com contains links to advertiser and partner websites. Please be aware that OurBabyNamer.com, is not responsible for the privacy practices of the advertisers or partners to whom we are linked. This privacy statement applies to our website only. Please review third party privacy policies prior to providing them any information. 

Service ProvidersWe may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. 

Google AdvertisementsGoogle, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads sites which contain their advertisements. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads based on your visit to this site and/or other sites on the internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. You may also choose to periodically clear your cookies via your browser in order to erase any cookies setup by various websites. 

Changes To Our Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy will be updated as necessary. Any changes to the policy will be posted to this page and will apply only to information collected after the modification date. This policy was last updated on August 25, 2009. 

Contact UsWe welcome your questions and comments. Please feel free to Contact Us if you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy. 

"We can easily forgive a child who is afraid of the dark; the real tragedy of life is when men are afraid of the light."  More
